http://www.dii.org/privacy-policy

Skip to main content (Press Enter).
LOG IN
Skip auxiliary navigation (Press Enter).
Contact DII
Skip main navigation (Press Enter).
Toggle navigation
Content types
AnnouncementsBlogsCommunitiesDiscussionsEventsGlossarySite ContentLibraries
Date range
on this day
between these dates
Posted by
HomeAbout DII About DIIDII PrinciplesSteering CommitteeWorking GroupMember CompaniesMembershipFeatured ToolsNews & EventsMember Connect
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
The Defense Industry Initiative (“DII”) is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and recognizes your right to keep personal information private. We reserve the right to change our privacy policy at any time. We will collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us. Any personal information provided to DII, including or similar to name, address, telephone number and e-mail address, will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of our organization, except as necessary to further the purpose for which you provide the information, with 3rd party providers that we have retained to perform services on our behalf (for example to host our website and send email communications), and to comply with legal requirements.When you visit our site to view any pages or use our online reference materials, you are free to browse our site without entering any personal information and therefore remain anonymous during your visit.While we do not collect identifying information about visitors to our site, we do automatically collect information about your visit for the strict purpose of tracking activity on our site, such as:
Internet domain and IP address from which you access our website;
type of browser and operating system used to access our site;
date and time you access our site;
pages you visit; and
If you linked to our site from another website, the address of that website.
Anti-Spam StatementThe DII may use your email to communicate about DII events, news, or other information. You may unsubscribe through links in every mailing or by using the ‘Contact Us’ feature on www.dii.org.Linking to this SiteYou may provide links to this site, provided that (a) you do not remove or obscure, by framing or otherwise, any portion of this Site, including any advertisements, terms of use or service, copyright notice, and other notices on this site, (b) you immediately deactivate and discontinue providing links to this site if requested by DII, and (c) DII may deactivate any link(s) at its discretion.Intellectual PropertyAll content and functionality on the site and other materials uploaded, downloaded or appearing on the site, including text, graphics, photos, button icons, images, digital downloads, data compilations, and software (collectively, “DII Content”) and the trademarks, service marks, designs, and logos (collectively, the “Trademarks”) are the exclusive property of DII or its licensors and are protected by copyright, trademark, and other laws of both the United States and foreign countries. Nothing in these Terms gives you a right to use the DII name or any of the Trademarks, logos, domain names, and other distinctive brand features or any confusingly similar. Limited LicenseDII grants you a personal, royalty-free, non-assignable and non-exclusive license to use the downloaded content as part of the services associated with the site. DII authorizes you to download and print a single copy of the content available from the site. The DII Content is to be used for your personal, non-commercial use only. You acquire absolutely no rights or licenses to the site including any materials contained within the site other than the limited right to utilize the Site in accordance with these Terms.Restrictions on UseYou must respect DII’s ownership and rights to the DII Content and Trademarks. You will not: (a) change or delete any proprietary notices from materials printed or downloaded from the Site; (b) refer to or attribute any information to DII or its licensors in any public medium (e.g., press release, websites) for advertising or promotion purposes, or for the purpose of informing or influencing any third party; (c) use or reproduce any Trademark of, or imply any endorsement by or relationship with, DII or its licensors; (d) modify, create derivative works of, decompile or otherwise attempt to extract source code from us, unless you are expressly permitted to do so under an open source license or we give you express written permission; (e) copy or adapt the HTML code used to generate web pages on the Site; (f) use or attempt to use engines, manual or automated software, tools, devices, agents, scripts robots or other means, devices, mechanisms or processes (including, but not limited to, browsers, spiders, robots, avatars or intelligent agents) to navigate, search, access, “scrape,” “crawl,” or “spider” any web pages or any services provided on the Sites other than the search engine and search agents available from DII on the Site and other than generally available third party web browsers (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari); or (g) aggregate, copy or duplicate in any manner any of the DII Content.Updated: May 7, 2019
Defense Industry Initiative
Privacy Policy
Member Terms and Conditions
Copyright 2019. All rights reserved.
Powered by Higher Logic
